A Guide to the Dickson Family Papers, 1769-1924
Special Collections, Virginia Tech
- Henry Frazier Dickson, 1841-1909
  - Financial accounts, 1863-1895
    - Items, 1863-1869 (Box 2, Folder 6)
      18 items.
    - Items, 1870-1871 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Items, 1872-1878 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Items, 1880-1895, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 9)
      36 items.
  - Account book, 1872-1892 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Diaries and daybooks, 1856-1883 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    Miscellaneous printed material; 7 items.
- Gearldine Dickson Burrow, 1879-1943
  - Correspondence and deeds, 1911-1923 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, 1924, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 13)
    22 items.
- Miscellaneous Materials
  - unspecified (Box 2, Folder 14)
    American history book (no title available), history to 1829.
  - Accompanient to Mitchell's Map, 1836 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    An Accompanient to Mitchell's Reference and Distance Map of the United States...(1836), owned by Rebecca Dickson (daughter of Robert).
  - Miscellaneous printed material from the Civil War years and newsclippings (Box 2, Folder 16)
    13 items (includes Confederate bonds.)
  - The Greenbrier Bugle, 1903-1906 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    2 items.
  - Genealogy charts and family records (Box 2, Folder 18)
    8 items (includes two pages pulled from the family Bible.)